

# **Hasin Rayan**

**Address:** South Banasree, Dhaka-1219, Bangladsh.

**Phone:** 01931584514

Email: <u>hasinrayan27@gmail.com</u>

#### **OBJECTIVE**

Pursuing a position in the mechanical design industry in which I can utilize and build upon my education, skills and past experiences in a way that is mutually beneficial to both and employer and allow for future growth and advancement.

# WORK EXPERIENCE

# \* CAD Operator at Tokyo Electric Power Service Co.

### Office: Matarbari Joint Venture Consultant

117, Kazi Nazrul Islam Avenue, Unique Height(18<sup>th</sup> Floor), Dhaka-1215 Project: Matarbari USC Coal fired Power Plant.

## 11th January, 2022 - Present

#### Responsibilities:

- Develop technical drawings using CAD software
- Make revisions and obtain approval from the Project Manager
- Prepare supporting documentation that includes product materials and dimensions
- Distribute drawings to internal departments and external contractors

# **❖** Assistant Engineer at *KDS Logistics Ltd*.

Sonaichari, Kumira, Chitagong-4314

#### 1st January, 2020 - 10 January, 2022

#### Responsibilities:

- Inspect vehicle engine and mechanical/electrical components to diagnose issues accurately
- Conduct routine maintenance work (replacing fluids, lubricating parts etc.) aiming to vehicle functionality and longevity
- Schedule future maintenance sessions and advise motorists on good vehicle use
- Repair or replace broken or dysfunctional parts and fix issues (e.g. leaks)
- Provide accurate estimates (cost, time, effort) for a repair or maintenance job
- Keep logs on work and issues
- Maintain equipment and tools in good condition

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# Site Engineer at Conveyor Logistics Ltd.

57 Kemal Ataturk Avenue Banani C/A, Dhaka 1213

### 5 January, 2019 - 29 December, 2019

#### Responsibilities:

- Logistics Operations
- Site Management
- Client Services
- **Customer Related Matters**

#### **EDUCATION**

# **Secondary School Certificate (SSC)**

Feni Govt. Pilot High School. Passed with GPA 4.63 out of 5.00 Commerce Section

# **Diploma in Mechanical Engineering**

Feni Polytechnic Institute Passed with GPA 2.86 out of 4.00 (Passing Year 2017)

# **B.Sc. in Mechanical Engineering**

Sonargaon University Enrolled Student (Currently Pursuing)

# **ADDITIONAL SKILLS**

- Solidworks
- AutoCAD
- Microsoft Word
- Adobe Illustrator
- MasterCAM
- CNC Machine
- Microsoft Excel
- Adobe Photoshop
- Mobile Application Development Github: https://github.com/zidni02

- Technical Drawing
- Microsoft PowerPoint
- WordPress Development

# Trainings / **Certifications**

# **CAD & CAM Design and Programming**

BEIOA-Light Engineering Training Institute (SEIP & ADB) Paradise Bhaban, 2 Folder Street, Wari, Dhaka

Duration: 25th April To 25th October, 2018

#### **Topic Covered:**

Solidworks, Master Cam, C.N.C. Machine, Technical Drawing

#### Auto Cad 2D & 3D

Bangladesh Industrial and Technical Assistance Center (BITAC) Sagorica Road, Chittagong-4219

Duration: 20th August to 28th September, 2017

#### **Topic Covered:**

AutoCAD Software, Technical Drawing

#### **Industrial Attachment**

Bangladesh Industrial and Technical Assistance Center (BITAC) Sagorica Road, Chittagong-4219

Duration: 1st August to 26th September, 2017

# Trainings / Certifications

# **Android Application Development**

National Academy for Computer Training and Research (NACTAR)

[Govt.]

Duration: 1 Month (January, 2021)

**Topic Covered:** 

Android Studio IDE, Android Programming, JAVA OOP, Android

Layout Design in XML Coding

Personal Information

Name : Hasin Rayan. Father's Name : Rezaul Karim. Mother's Name : Khaleda Sultana.

Permanent Address : 456, Mizan Road, Feni Sadar.

Date of Birth : 27<sup>th</sup> November, 1997. Nationality : Bangladeshi (By Birth).

Religion : Islam. Marital Status : Single.

Mobile : +8801931584514

### References

# **Mohammed Shahid Ullah**

Executive Director (Finance)

Company: Coal Power Generation Company Bangladesh

Limited (CPGCBL)

Address: Unique Heights (Level 17), 117, Kazi Nazrul Islam

Avenue, Dhaka-1217.

Cell: +8801730798097, +8801716383259.

**Candidate Signature**